BRIAN T CARDINES

South Jersey, NJ 07080 | bcardi@gmail.com | 905-405-9752

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Highly skilled moldable, motivated person with versatile experience. Various leadership experience as a registered nurse for over ten years, including charge RN, EPIC superuser

- Skills & Abilities HTML / CSS / Bootstrap
 - Javascript
 - Jquery
 - Server side API
 - Node JS. Express
 - MySQL, MongoDB, Mongoose
 - React
 - MERN

EXPERIENCE

RN Care Coordinator New York Presbyterian Lower Manhattan, NY, NY 05/2017 - PRESENT

- Daily utilization review
- Experience with Medicaid, Medicare, and managed HMO, protocol and procedures
- Proficient with Interqual Criteria
- Floated throughout many diciplines including icu, medical, emergency department
- Named 2018 Case Manager of the year for exceptional work and improving the standards for discharges in the ICU
- RN Super-User for new EPIC computer documentation systems

RN CARE COORDINATOR CLARA MAASS MEDICAL CENTER - BELLEVILLE. NJ 06/2015 - 05/201

RN EMERGENCY DEPARTMENT SAINT BARNABAS MEDICAL CENTER - LIVINGSTON, NJ 06/2012 to 06/2015

- Firstnet computer documentation system superuser
- Charge RN ED
- Delegate task to ancillary personnel, RN, MD

SURGICAL TELEMETRY STROKE STEPDOWN SAINT BARNABAS MEDICAL CENTER – LIVINGSTON, NJ

06/2010 to 06/2012

EDUCATION KEAN UNIVERSITY, UNION, NJ

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN NURSING

MOUNTAINSIDE HOSPITAL SCHOOL OF NURSING, MONTCLAIR, NJ

RN DIPLOMA

REFERENCES AVAILABLE UPON REQUEST